🔀 yuliia.dobrova@gmail.com

1 +1(778)-325-3487

O Vancouver, BC, Canada

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced Front End Software Developer with a history of over 5 years in application and website development. Worked on various projects, from developing solo-projects to contributing to social media platforms and school management systems, participated in collaborative Git usage. Technical background in Civil Design-Engineering holding a Bachelor's degree, offering over 10 years of both executive and management positions.

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- REST API
- React
- Redux Toolkit
- Axios
- WebSocket
- Flexbox, Grid
- Parcel, Webpack
- Preprocessor SASS (SCSS)
- Material-UI
- Bootstrap, jQuery
- Styled-components
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- NoSQL
- Postman
- Swagger
- JWT (JSON Web token)
- Git
- GitHub
- Vercel, Netlify, Heroku
- Visual Studio Code
- Copilot
- NPM, Yarn
- Responsive/Adaptive design
- Agile, Scrum
- UI / UX Design Principles
- Figma
- Slack
- PM Tools (Click-Up, Jira)

YULIIA DOBROVA

FRONT END SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

Front End Software Developer at Research and production enterprise "Ukrradioprom" LLC (April 2023 - January 2024)

• Developed a user-friendly web application to efficiently handle clients product database, which resulted in a significant 20% increase in online sales within a period of 6 months.

Front End Software Developer at Web Tech Company "TensionX" ("SaaS Insiders") (February 2022 - March 2023)

- Contributed to collaborative Git practices while working with a team of up to 7 developers, successfully delivering to the customer a Social Media Platform meeting deadline in 3 months.
- Improved user functionality in an existing School Management System application.

Front End Software Developer at Dental Center of Dr. Krolyk (November 2021 - January 2022)

• Created a website design from scratch and developed it for my client in 2 months (implemented interactivity, real reviews, geolocation, multilingualism, adapted to different devices, deployed to hosting).

Civil Design Engineer / Head of the Project Department / Front End Software Developer Engineering Company

"Avtomagistral" LCC (September 2018 - February 2021)

- Holding the title of Civil Design Engineer with the certificate (license), created drawings in AutoCAD, was engaged in project approvals, supervised the author's projects during construction.
- Directed a team of 30 diverse engineers: geodetic engineers, design engineers, accountant engineers. Completed of 50 infrastructure building projects for new design or reconstruction (roads, bridges, park areas, networks) within a 6 month period meeting deadline.
- Created a multi-page business card website for the company from scratch.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer Course

GoIT - International Ed-Tech Company (2021)

Bachelor's Degree in Water Resources Engineering

The Faculty of Geography, National University of Kyiv, Ukraine (2009)

LANGUAGES

• English (fluent) • Ukrainian (fluent) • Russian (fluent)

WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO AND PROFILES

https://yuliiadobrova.com/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yuliia-dobrova/

https://github.com/YuliaDobrova